http://www.2mhost.com/privacy-policy.html

Effective
Date:
April 17, 2018
Please read this policy and if you have any questions Contact us.
By using the site you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this policy.
TWO M HOST FZE is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection, use and disclosure of personal information. The terms of this policy apply to all personal information collected by TWO M HOST FZE on the website 2mhost.com and other country-specific TWO M HOST FZE websites which may be linked to 2mhost.com. If you have any questions or concerns, please Contact us
For personal information protection purposes in the European Union, TWO M HOST FZE is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of the personal information.
Privacy Officer
We have designated a privacy officer to be accountable for our policies
and practices with respect to the management of personal information.
You may forward any questions,
comments or complaints that you might have about this privacy policy by email to: privacy _at_ 2mhost.com
Collection of Your Non-Personal and Personal Information
TWO M HOST FZE collects certain kinds of non-personal information,
such as the website that referred you to us,
browser type and language, and access times.
We also may collect navigational information,
including information about the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions taken in connection with the site.
We only collect personal information about you after you have provided us with your consent to collect that specific information.
Personal information includes
information collected when you register or visit the site including your member name and password, your name, your mailing address, email address, IP address and phone number.
information collected when you make a purchase including your credit card number and billing address.
Collecting this information is required for us to process your service related requests.
Use of Your Personal Information
TWO M HOST FZE collects and uses your personal information to:
create and manage your hosting account;
process your transactions;
process your domain registration and transfer requests;
to display content that is customized to your preference and to run Interactive Areas
to communicate with you about your transactions and transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations; and;
to communicate with you about your services such as upgrade/migration letters, maintenance notifications
Personal information collected by TWO M HOST FZE may be stored and processed
in USA or any other country in which TWO M HOST FZE or its agents maintain facilities,
and by providing us with your personal information and using our sites or services,
you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.
If you would like to know more about our privacy practices or if you would like to exercise any of your personal
information protection rights (including the right to have your personal information deleted),
please contact our Privacy Officer.
Disclosing Your Personal Information
TWO M HOST FZE does not sell your personal information to any third-parties.
Except as set out in this privacy policy, TWO M HOST FZE does not disclose personal information to any third-parties.
We may disclose your personal information to third-party service providers who perform
services on our behalf. For example, we may use other companies to handle the processing of payments,
to provide domain registration, to provide tech. support, etc. Those third-party service providers
(i) shall be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service,
(ii) must protect personal information to the same extent as TWO M HOST FZE, and (iii)
shall be prohibited from using it for any other purpose.
Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required or permitted to do so by law.
Consent of Your Personal Information
By submitting personal information to us, you acknowledge and agree that you have consented to the collection, use and disclosure practices set out in this Privacy Policy as they relate to your personal information.
Accessing Your Personal Information
If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us,
you may access and change your personal information in the "Clients Login" section of the site.
Personal Information Preferences
At this time, we only send you service-related communications; generally you may not opt-out of these types of communications.
Use of Cookies and Other Technologies
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. If you reject cookies, you will not able to manage your hosting account using our password protected area.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. Please be aware that the site is optimally designed to operate with cookies enabled in your internet browser. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies but you will be able to perform basic navigation through the site. Disabling cookies may negatively impact your experience of the site.
Security of Your Personal Information
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal information including without limitation:
limiting access to your personal information to those of our employees who require it to provide services to you;
requiring employees to sign confidentiality agreements to protect customer and other confidential information;
ensuring that third-party service providers sign confidentiality agreements to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and not to use it for any unauthorized purposes;
personal information collected is retained as long as it is reasonably required for the purposes it was collected;
encrypting credit card information on our order forms using secure socket layer (SSL) technology;and
storing your personal information in secure computer systems which protect it from unauthorized access or use.
TWO M HOST FZE does not store credit cards information.
No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If a password is used to protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.
Children
We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18.
If you are under 18, you shall not use or enter information on this site.
Links
We may link to websites, including those of our subsidiaries and third-party content providers, that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.
Additional Policy Information
With your
consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.
If you
want your testimonial removed please contact our Privacy Officer.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy. If there are material changes to this statement or in how iStockphoto will use your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit one of our sites.
This website is using cookies, 2MHost privacy policy
